<d id="D_TA" m="TA" n="Technical Analysis Indicators (TA)" d="Technical Analysis Indicators (TA)." xmlns:in="http://schemas.reuters.com/ns/2007/08/snapshotmeta_internal" xmlns:out="http://schemas.reuters.com/ns/2007/08/snapshotmeta" xmlns="http://schemas.reuters.com/ns/2007/08/snapshotmeta_parts">
	<c id="C_TA_A" m="A" n="Analysis (A)" d="Analysis (TS).">
		<i id="I_TA_A_ExponentialMovingAverage" d="The Exponential Moving Average analysis is similar to a weighted moving average analysis in that they both assign greater weight to the most recent data. However, an Exponential Moving Average uses all of the data available going back from the point being calculated; the older the data the less weighting it is given. Thus, for the calculation of a five period Exponential Moving Average, all of the price data in the life of the instrument is used, but, in the calculation of an equivalent Weighted Moving Average, only five data points are used. The Exponential Moving Average is another method of weighting a moving average." l="Exponential Moving Average" i="A:1L A:AN A:AP A:FP A:FR A:FQ A:AQ A:FN A:1W A:31 A:FS A:AR A:32 A:AT A:AU A:33 A:34 A:35 A:36 A:37 A:FU A:FT A:10 A:39 A:3A A:AS A:2R A:BF A:BG A:BH A:BI A:BJ A:3C A:3B A:3F A:1X A:FV A:FX A:FW A:18 A:FZ A:FY A:AV I:17 I:50 A:2X A:KZ A:L0 A:L1 A:L2 A:L3 A:L4 A:L5 A:L6 A:5M A:2Y" n="TA.A.ExponentialMovingAverage" s="TA" cc="ricPeriodValue" pc="TaSma" vp="4" vu="N" isScreen="false">
			<in:sp k="taFunction">ExponentialMovingAverage</in:sp>
			<in:sp k="taColumnForValue">EMA</in:sp>
		</i>
		<i id="I_TA_A_MACD" d="Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) is a type of oscillator that can measure market momentum as well as follow or indicate the trend. The convention for the MACD analysis is to use an Exponential Moving Average (EMA). MACD consists of two lines, the MACD Line and the Signal Line. The MACD Line measures the difference between a short moving average and a long moving average. The Signal Line is a moving average of the MACD Line. MACD oscillates above and below a zero line without upper and lower boundaries. The MACD and the Signal Lines are plotted together in a subchart. Note that there is another form of MACD, which displays the difference between the MACD and the Signal Lines as a forest line." l="MACD" i="A:1L A:AN A:AP A:FP A:FR A:FQ A:AQ A:FN A:1W A:31 A:FS A:AR A:32 A:AT A:AU A:33 A:34 A:35 A:36 A:37 A:FU A:FT A:10 A:39 A:3A A:AS A:2R A:BF A:BG A:BH A:BI A:BJ A:3C A:3B A:3F A:1X A:FV A:FX A:FW A:18 A:FZ A:FY A:AV I:17 I:50 A:2X A:KZ A:L0 A:L1 A:L2 A:L3 A:L4 A:L5 A:L6 A:5M A:2Y" n="TA.A.MACD" s="TA" cc="macdcc" pc="TaMACD" vp="4" vu="N" isScreen="false">
			<in:sp k="taFunction">MACD</in:sp>
			<in:sp k="taColumnForValue">MACD:MACD|MACDSignal:MACD Signal</in:sp>
		</i>
		<i id="I_TA_A_RelativeStrengthIndex" d="The Relative Strength Index (RSI) is a price-following oscillator that ranges between 0 and 100. A popular method of analyzing the RSI is to look for a divergence in which the security is making a new high but the RSI is failing to surpass its previous high. This divergence is an indication of an impending reversal." l="Relative Strength Index (RSI)" i="A:1L A:AN A:AP A:FP A:FR A:FQ A:AQ A:FN A:1W A:31 A:FS A:AR A:32 A:AT A:AU A:33 A:34 A:35 A:36 A:37 A:FU A:FT A:10 A:39 A:3A A:AS A:2R A:BF A:BG A:BH A:BI A:BJ A:3C A:3B A:3F A:1X A:FV A:FX A:FW A:18 A:FZ A:FY A:AV I:17 I:50 A:2X A:KZ A:L0 A:L1 A:L2 A:L3 A:L4 A:L5 A:L6 A:5M A:2Y" n="TA.A.RelativeStrengthIndex" s="TA" cc="ricPeriodValue" pc="TaRSI" vp="4" vu="N" isScreen="false">
			<in:sp k="taFunction">RSI</in:sp>
			<in:sp k="taColumnForValue">RSI</in:sp>
		</i>
		<i id="I_TA_A_SimpleMovingAverage" d="Simple Moving Averages are the most common and popular form of Moving Average. The primary reason for this is the relative ease with which Simple Moving Averages are calculated and their effectiveness in a trending market. A Simple Moving Average is calculated by adding values over a set number of periods and then dividing the sum by the total number of values. As with other types of Moving Averages, Simple Moving Averages smooth the data by removing noise over the selected period. The ability to smooth data makes them a useful tool in identifying price trends and trend reversals." l="Simple Moving Average" i="A:1L A:AN A:AP A:FP A:FR A:FQ A:AQ A:FN A:1W A:31 A:FS A:AR A:32 A:AT A:AU A:33 A:34 A:35 A:36 A:37 A:FU A:FT A:10 A:39 A:3A A:AS A:2R A:BF A:BG A:BH A:BI A:BJ A:3C A:3B A:3F A:1X A:FV A:FX A:FW A:18 A:FZ A:FY A:AV I:17 I:50 A:2X A:KZ A:L0 A:L1 A:L2 A:L3 A:L4 A:L5 A:L6 A:5M A:2Y" n="TA.A.SimpleMovingAverage" s="TA" cc="ricPeriodValue" pc="TaSma" vp="4" vu="N" isScreen="false">
			<in:sp k="taFunction">SimpleMovingAverage</in:sp>
			<in:sp k="taColumnForValue">SMA</in:sp>
		</i>
	</c>
</d>